

Evgenii RUDAKOV

MACHINE LEARNING SPECIALIST

in @evgenii-rudakov-a4aba2179

@dolphin-in-a-coma

Second year MSc student in Biometrcis and CV. Erasmus Mundus Scholarship holder with almost 2 years of industrial experience. I am very interested in both the development of machine learning methods and their application to solving real-world problems.

Date of birth 22/07/1995

eugenartemovich@gmail.com

+33 7 49 29 28 82

Paris

Publication

Multi-Task CNN model for emotion recognition from EEG Brain maps

Authors: Evgenii Rudakov, Lou Laurent, Valentin Cousin, Ahmed Roshdi, Regis Fournier, Amine Nait-ali, Taha Beyrouthy, Samer Al Kork

IEEE 4th International Conference on Bioengineering for Smart Technologies, 2021 [Paper], [Code], [Slides], [Video]

Best Masters Student Paper Award

Languages

Russian Native

English Advanced IELTS Academic 2019: 6.5/9

French/German Elementary

Honors & Awards

Erasmus Mundus Joint Master Degree Scholarship

2020, University Jean Monnet

Bachelor Diploma with Honor

2020, RTU MIREA

Scientific National Olympiad Prize-winner

New Economic School Olympiad

2019, Mathematics

Scientific National Olympiads Finalist

- All-Russian Olympiad "I'm a professional" 2019, Software Engineering
- Moscow State University Universide 2019, Applied Mathematics
- American Center Hackathon 2019, Big Data

Other Interests

Learning something unpractical

Discovering of cultures and people

Trying to make electronic music

Reading fiction

Work experience

Machine Learning Researcher 05/2019 - 08/2020

Huawei Moscow, Russia

Speech Techologies: Voice Biometry, VAD, ASR

Machine Learning Engineer 04/2019 - 05/2019

PharmHub Moscow, Russia

Natural Language Processing: Text Classification, Entity Extraction

02/2019 - 04/2019 Machine Learning Researcher Intern

Tinkoff Bank Moscow, Russia

Natural Language Processing: Text Classification, Language Models

10/2018 - 12/2018 **Software Engineer Intern**

HeadHunter Moscow, Russia

09/2017 - 12/2017 **Marketing Project Coordinator Assistant**

ITM Moscow, Russia

Education

Erasmus Mundus Master (PSRS), Biometrics and Intelligent Vision 2020 - 2022

Joint Degree

Université Paris-Est Créteil France

University of Eastern Finland Finland

Université Jean Monnet France

Politecnico di Torino Italy

Bachelor of Computer Science in Economics 2016 - 2020

MIREA - Russian Technological University Moscow, Russia

GPA: 4.93/5

Online Courses 2018 - 2021

Machine Learning (Open Data Science);

Deep Learning Introduction (NSU, Open Data Science); Introduction to Machine Learning (HSE, Coursera); Introduction to SQL (Computer Science Center, Stepic);

Algorithms: theory and practice (Computer Science Center, Stepic)

Technical Skills

Confident with

Python: PyTorch, Keras, Tensorflow 2, Numpy, SciPy, Scikit-Learn, Matplotlib, Pandas... Practical: ML, Deep Learning, Computer Vision, Image Processing, NLP, Speech Analysis

Theoretical: Probability, Statistics, Advanced Mathematics

Programing: Algorithms, Data Structures, OOP Other instruments: SQL, Git, Excel/VBA

Can work with

Tensorflow 1., Matlab, LaTeX, Linux/Bash, Unity

Have experience with

C/C++, C#, Java, JavaScript, HTML/CSS, Ableton